And it is exactly in these areas of greatest pain and fragility that the miracle is already taking place.
It's like a seed under the ground. You can't see what's happening.
But the most important processes are unfolding in the silence, in the darkness,
preparing the manifestation that will change everything.
You often look at the clock of your life and think it's already too late.
But in my kingdom, it is never too late.
I am the God who transforms deserts into flower gardens, who makes dry bones revive,
who brings back what seemed lost forever.
Remember Sarah, who laughed when she found out she would have a child in her old age.
How did my servant Abraham wait decades for the promise?
And yet, at the appointed time, the impossible happened.
The same applies to you. The pain you feel now is making room for a miracle
that wouldn't fit into your life otherwise. That closed.
You all that disappointed him so much wasn't a rejection. It was a redirection.
I was sparing you from paths that would divert you from your true destiny.
From this great miracle that I am preparing.
I want you to understand something fundamental.
My miracles are not just for solving problems.
They offer the purpose of revealing my glory and expanding my kingdom.
The miracle I am preparing is not just for your personal comfort,
although it will bring you unspeakable joy.
It has ramifications you can't even imagine.
Think of Lazarus, who was resurrected after four days.
That miracle was not just to return. And brother to Martha and Mary.
It was a testimony that strengthened the faith of many, and that even today,
thousands of years later confirms the power of my child Jesus.
Your miracle will also touch lives. You don't even know yet.
There are people designated to cross your path, who will be impacted by the story of what I am going to do in your life.
Your own family will see my glory through this miracle, and generations will be transformed.
There is an eternal purpose behind the supernatural manifestation I am preparing.
I know you've tried everything, he consulted experts, followed advice,
implemented strategies, took medications, made investments, tried new methods.
And it seems like nothing completely worked.
This is because this specific problem does not have an earthly solution.
It has been reserved for a demonstration of my supernatural power.
There are situations in life that no human effort can resolve.
They were designed specifically for my intervention, not to punish you,
but to create the perfect setting where my glory can be revealed in an unmistakable way.
Do you remember when my child multiplied the loads and fishes?
He could have just sent everyone home to get food.
The lack of resources created the perfect scenario for one of the most iconic miracles recorded.
Likewise, the limitations you face now are not obstacles to the miracle.
They are the stage on which it will be demonstrated.
Now I want you to understand the pattern that always precedes my great miracles.
Before liberation comes, the most intense captivity.
Before healing, the disease often worsens.
Before financial provision is made, resources are often completely exhausted.
Are you living in this moment right now?
Does it feel like everything is getting worse instead of better?
This is not a sign that I have abandoned you.
It is often the prelude to the greatest miracle.
It's like the darkest night before the most glorious dawn.
The sources and the people of Israel saw the Red Sea open only when they were trapped,
when the Egyptian army had their backs and the sea in front of them.
It was in the moment of greatest despair that my power manifested itself most dramatically.
You may be feeling now that you have hit rock bottom, that there is nowhere left to go,
and you are right, there is nowhere left to go, but up to the manifestation of the miracle that is already determined.
I want you to know that this is exactly the point where I begin to operate most powerfully,
and now let me tell you about this heavenly intercession that is taking place on your behalf.
There is a cloud of witnesses, people who lived on this earth before you,
and who are now in my presence, who rejoice to see the persistent faith.
You demonstrate even without seeing its conjoys people who lived on this earth with your behalf.
There is a part of this heaven begin to operate most powerfully,
and now let me tell you about this heavenly intercession that is taking place on your behalf.
There is a cloud of witnesses, people who lived on this earth before you,
and who are now in my presence, who rejoice to see the persistent faith.
You demonstrate even without seeing its complete fulfillment,
that grandmother who prayed for you before you were even born,
who has still alive before my throne, that has been passed and interceded for the next generation.
The fruit of your ministry is manifesting in your life now.
There is a spiritual continuity that transcends time and physical death.
This communion of saints is not something you should invoke or seek directly.
That would be overstepping the boundaries I have sent.
But it is a reality that should comfort your heart.
The prayers of the departed righteous remain effective,
not because they have power of their own,
but because they align with my perfect will for your life.
When you pray, know that you do not pray alone,
your voice joins a heavenly choir that has declared my will over your life for generations.
This is part of the glorious mystery of the body of Christ,
that transcends time and space,
and more than that my own child Jesus is on my right hand.
Continually interceding for you,
the Holy Spirit within you grows,
within expressible size,
when you don't even know how to pray.
You are enveloped in a triple projection of divine intercession.
Have you ever felt an inexplicable peace in the midst of solutions
that should have you?
You are in with a continuous,
but you declare my will over your life for generations.
This is part of the glorious mystery of the body of Christ,
that transcends time and space,
and more than that my own child Jesus is on my right hand.
Continually interceding for you,
the Holy Spirit within you grows,
within expressible size,
when you don't even know how to pray.
You are enveloped in a triple projection of divine intercession.
Have you ever felt an inexplicable peace in the midst of solutions?
Next generation,
with a brilliant symmetry,
it's a bit better.
This is not a sign that I have abandoned you.
It is often the prelude to the greatest miracle.
It's like the darkest night before the most glorious dawn.
Moses of the people of Israel
saw the Red Sea open only when they were trapped,
with the Egyptian army of their backs,
and the sea in front of them.
It was in the moment that the greatest despair
that might now manifest itself most dramatic.
You may be feeling now that you have hit rock bottom,
that there is nowhere left to go,
and you are right,
there is nowhere left to go,
but up to the manifestation of the miracle
that is already determined.
I want you to know that this is exactly the point
where I begin to operate most powerfully.
And now,
let me tell you about this heavenly intercession
that is taking place on your behalf.
There is a cloud of witnesses,
people who lived on this earth before you,
and who are now in my presence,
who rejoice to see the persistent faith.
You demonstrate,
even without seeing its complete fulfillment.
That grandmother who prayed for you
before you were even born,
your prayers are still alive before my throne,
that faithful pastor who interceded for the next generation,
the fruit of your ministry is manifesting in your life now.
There is a spiritual continuity that transcends time
and physical death.
This communion of saints is not something
you should invoke or seek directly.
That would be overstepping the boundaries I have said.
But it is a reality that should comfort your heart.
The prayers of the departed righteous remain effective,
not because they have power of their own,
but because they align with my perfect will for your life.
When you pray, know that you do not pray alone,
your voice joins a heavenly choir
that has declared my will over your life for generations.
This is part of the glorious mystery of the body of Christ
that transcends time and space,
more than that my own child Jesus is at my right hand,
continually interceding for you.
The Holy Spirit within you groans,
within expressible size,
when you don't even know how to pray.
You are enveloped in a triple protection of divine intercession.
Have you ever felt an inexplicable peace
in the midst of circumstances
that should reshatter in your spirit?
This is the tangible result of this heavenly intercession
combined with my supernatural will.
It is the fruit of this communion of saints
that process the veil between heaven and earth.
Now I want to tell you something practical
about the miracle that is about to happen.
It will come in a way you don't expect,
in a way you don't imagine.
My greatest miracles often come disguised in surprising ways.
Joseph awaited in prison,
not knowing that he was a dream away from the palace.
Esther was a simple young Jewish girl
without imagining that she would be queen
and save an entire nation.
David was just a shepherd when he was appointed to begin.
Your miracle probably won't come wrapped up the way you expect.
It can come through someone you would never imagine.
In a way that defies your expectations,
that's why it's so important to keep your heart open
and your eyes attentive.
Many people have missed their miracles
because they were looking in the wrong direction.
They were so fixated on how they thought the answer would come
that they didn't recognize when it came differently.
Don't make that mistake, son.
If you are looking for a fuller and more fulfilled life,
divine dialogue is the perfect tool for you.
With powerful techniques and clear instructions,
you can achieve the peace and personal fulfillment you've always wanted.
Don't waste any more time.
Access the link in the pinned comment
and take the first step towards a better life.
Your part now is to prepare to receive
as cultivating an attitude of expectation and gratitude.
Start giving thanks for the miracle before you even see it.
This is not...
The peace and personal fulfillment you've always wanted.
Don't waste any more time.
Access the link in the pinned comment
and take the first step towards a better life.
Your part now is to prepare to receive
as cultivating an attitude of expectation and gratitude.
Start giving thanks for the miracle before you even see it.
This is not denial of reality.
It is the highest expression of faith.
When my child Jesus, before the tomb of Lazarus,
gave thanks before seeing the miracle,
he was demonstrating the most powerful principle of the kingdom,
gratitude in advance.
Start giving thanks for the miracle as if it had already happened
because in heavenly reality it has already happened.
Talk about your miracle in the present tense.
Don't say, God will heal me.
Say, I thank you because I am healed by His wounds.
Don't say, I hope God restores my marriage.
Say, I thank God for the complete restoration
He has already accomplished in my home.
This is not a positive thinking technique.
It is alignment with the spiritual reality
that already exists in the kingdom.
If you can create a feeling in your heart,
0.1 hurts.
The math feeling is going to harmonize your heart and your brain.
Precepts.
Frit?
It's no glyco.
Disapair entry.
You with pan.
Needles.
I'm not sure you have a makes up.
We used to make movies.
We used to call it Sprite.
We're going to wash these up a little bit.
I like to wash them.
I'm going to get some of the bugs out.
So we're going to go ahead and cut these off.
All we're going to do now.
I like to cut them up.
I'm going to cut them in half, y'all.
Drop this half in here.
I don't even know who showed me how to do this.
Take them away.
I don't get them down.
Sugar.
I like to cook one.
Two.
Three.
Four.
A little bit more.
Next thing, all you do is put water in.
Always put it to the top.
I like to shake it up.
Get that sugar melting.
See the sugar is all on the bottom here.
Get it all melted.
And what happens when the sugar permeates?
The sugar permeates with the pan.
So the pan will put off yeast and make it permeate.
And once it does that, that's what makes it like carbonation.
It makes it taste like the first one.
All right, y'all.
We got them all made up.
Yeah, we got to do it hurry up and wait again.
Seems like everything I do, I got to hurry up and wait.
We're going to let this sit here for about three, four days.
All right, y'all.
It's been about four, five days.
We've been waiting.
We've heard it pop.
That means it's ready.
OK, now we've got fans.
And now I've got a little strainer.
Well, when it's heated, we didn't handle strainer.
We just drank it straight from the jar.
OK, we're going to dump something in here.
Sure, y'all.
Y'all see all the fans on the top?
See that?
Oh, smells so good.
All right, y'all.
Catch a few of the needles.
All right.
Y'all the fans in there, y'all.
And y'all see that?
Yeah, I got some little tasting cups here.
Well, I'm fans of the day, I know.
Bring back childhood memory.
Childhood memory, you see it.
It's really good.
This looked like a disappearing tree.
You were fine, needle.
I'm not sure you had to make something,
but we used to make movies for kids.
And we used to call it Sprite.
We're going to wash these up a little bit.
I like to wash them.
I'm going to get some of the bugs out.
So we're going to go ahead and cut these off.
All we're going to do now.
I like to cut them up.
I'm going to cut them in half, y'all.
Drop this half in here.
I don't even know how to show me how to do this.
But shake them around and get them down.
Show them.
I like to learn.
That's so important right now.
It is bringing into the visible
what has already been declared in the invisible.
Another crucial part of your preparation is forgiveness.
You cannot receive fully while holding resentments.
That person who heard you deeply,
that family member who betrayed you,
that colleague who wronged you,
you need to release them through genuine forgiveness.
I understand this.
They seem impossible considering the pain they caused.
But I'm not asking you to forget or to say
that what they did was right.
I'm asking you to release them from the prison of your resentment
and place the situation completely in my hands.
Forgiveness is not a feeling.
It is a decision.
It is an act of your will that frees not only the other person,
but mainly yourself.
A miracle I have prepared requires a clean heart to fully manifest.
Don't let roots of bitterness block what I'm about to do.
Now do you feel that hesitation in your heart,
that fear of being disappointed again?
I understand perfectly.
You've had so many disappointed hopes,
so many promises that didn't seem to,
who come true in the time you expected.
But I want you to know that this hesitation
is not a pen to my heart.
I understand you have a frailty.
Remember Thomas who needed to see to believe.
My child did not condemn him.
He revealed himself to him in the way he needed.
If you are struggling with doubts,
come to me just as you are.
Bring your doubts, your fears, your questions.
I prefer your vulnerable honesty to false certainty.
Even with faith as small as a must and seed,
you can move mountains.
It's not the size of your faith that matters.
It's the object of it.
And when your faith is placed in me,
even shaky and imperfect,
it is enough to see my miracles manifest.
I want you to share with me in the comments.
What is this miracle you are waiting for?
What is this mountain that seems impossible to move?
By declaring your need,
you are taking the first step towards seeing manifestation.
Now let me tell you about divine timing.
My timing rarely matches your expectations.
For you, the weight may feel like torture.
For me, it is the necessary process of preparation.
Remember how the people of Israel wandered for 40 years
before entering the Promised Land.
Those were not wasted years.
There were years of forming a national identity
of learning dependence on me
of preparing for the battles to come.
Likewise, your waiting time
is not wasted time.
It's a precious time
where I'm working on levels you can't see.
Preparing not just the miracle,
but preparing you for the miracle.
Because you see,
sometimes the biggest challenges
and receiving the miracle,
it's keeping it.
Many people have received blessings
that they were not emotionally or spiritually prepared for
and have lost them.
Your waiting has a profound purpose of preparation.
Have you ever wondered why Lazarus had to spend four days
in the tomb before being resurrected?
Why didn't my child arrive before he died?
Or at least on the first day?
Because I wanted to eliminate any doubt about the miracle.
After four days, according to Jewish beliefs,
the soul had definitively departed
and decomposition was advanced.
It was humanly impossible.
And that is exactly where my power shines brightest.
Perhaps your situation has also reached this point of human impossibility.
The doctors have already given up.
Financial advisors have exhausted their options.
Marriage therapists have already recommended divorce.
Perfect.
Now we are exactly where my supernatural power can be demonstrated
beyond a shadow of a doubt.
My child, my daughter,
you have tried to resolve this on your own for so long.
You have already exhausted your resources, your wisdom, your strength.
Now finally, we come to the place where you can truly rest
and see my salvation manifest.
While you wait, cultivate peace.
Not that superficial peace that depends on circumstances,
but the deep peace that comes from knowing
that I am in control even when everything seems chaotic.
It is a peace that transcends human understanding,
that guards your heart and mind,
even in the midst of the most violent storm.
And don't forget to take care of your physical being while you wait.
Rest adequately.
Eat well.
Move your body.
Sometimes we focus so much on the spiritual
that we neglect the physical temple I created for you to inhabit.
Your body, mind and spirit are interconnected,
and comprehensive care is part of preparing for the miracle.
There is something else I want you to know.
This miracle I am preparing for you is not isolated.
It's part of a bigger plan that includes your family, your community,
and even people you don't know yet.
When Daniel prayed, he did not know that his prayers were moving angelic arms.
When Esther fasted, she did not fully understand how their actions
would save an entire nation.
Likewise, your personal miracle is connected to a much greater purpose
than you can see now.
People will watch what I do in their lives
and find hope for their own battles.
Your testimony will open doors.
This is why it is so important that you begin sharing your faith expectation
even before you see the full manifestation.
Tell people what you expect me to do,
not out of vanity or presumption,
but as an act of faith that glorifies me.
Remember, the enemy wants you to keep quiet about your expectations
so that if you don't see the miracle right away,
he can use that to shame you.
Don't fall into this trap, openly declare your trust in me,
knowing that my word never returns void.
Share in the comments what miracle are you waiting for.
What seems impossible in your life right now,
I will read each comment and pray as will be released on your behalf.
Now let's talk about how you will know when the miracle is about to happen.
I often sense signs, little confirmations, divine coincidences,
words of knowledge through others,
keep your spiritual eyes and ears wide,
open often before the greatest miracle.
There is a period of intensifying spiritual warfare.
The enemy, sensing that he is about to lose ground,
launches his fiercest attacks.
Don't be alarmed if just as you are getting closer to manifestation,
things seem to temporarily get worse.
It's just the last spasm of darkness before the glorious door.
You may also notice an increase in prophetic dreams
or spiritual impressions.
Pay attention to them, write them down.
Compare them with my written word.
Don't dismiss these subtle communications.
Shit!